Okay, so, creating the thumbnail for
this next video for Florinpop.
Uhm,
I made 500k from different income streams.
I made 500k from my project, here's my playbook.
Yeah, uhm, the path basically provided some feedback.
I'm and, uhm,
I actually agree with it a lot.
This concept of the thumbnails where it shows like
this, kinda like the breakdown of their income streams or this multipreneur
guy, yeah, that shows the breakdown of
different income streams like that on screen. So what we did in the previous
thumbnail, where it's just huge text on screen,
that doesn't look realistic, which is a,
which is really good feedback, so we'll not do that again,
we'll come up with something else, but first let's see what,
where is it, let's see what this guy provided us with.
All right,
so we'll definitely, we'll definitely not using this one,
and we'll definitely not using this one, uh,
what we're doing again for this thumbnail is we're going for a two thumbnail
test, thumbnail one is clean,
simple, no text, just guest at the,
at desk slash work environment.
And thumbnail two is we're going to do the usual one,
uhm, with text on screen.
So, yeah,
we're not using this one. Here his laptop is too far
away. This one is good.
We'll use this one. We'll
see
how
we can tweak it, maybe,
potentially. And we're using this one,
definitely. Okay,
let's just, let's just generate some
extra space for us to,
do I have my, yeah, I have my headphones, uhm,
sorry, let's just generate some extra space.
So it's gonna be MagicExpand,
and we'll just, we'll just do this.
Canvas, uh, Canvas MagicExpand feature is really good,
actually, we definitely wanna
use it. Okay,
we'll just go for the cleanest one.
Up here, but I don't even think we need to.
Looking at this composition, it looks pretty good.
So, in the, uhm, in the title,
we have, we have 500k text.
Uh,
let's grab
But, what we'll also experiment with,
is,
so, okay, we can make this one 500k.
And then, potentially, even moving him to the side to
make the text a bit bigger. Yeah,
you know, it sucks a little bit, because I would like,
Nah,
it's just not good, it's, It's way too,
Way too below. Uh,
or way too, Way too far,
From the face.
So here's what we'll do.
I would love to,
Do this type of thumbnail. Does he
say a cool
MRR, Number?
Don't
think so.
Yes, 500k over six years.
That's going to be not a good number.
We're not putting 7k,
7k MRR in the title or in the thumbnail.
Okay, so we'll just do, we'll just do,
we'll just do 500k like this.
And then for this one,
you know, this is kind of interesting. An issue with this photo,
like if you look at this photo, it's so much better just because again
the laptop is just closer.
So we would need to do some Photoshop magic there.
I'm thinking, or potentially,
can we do it in Canva? If I just do BG remover,
Yeah, yeah, I wish Canva had selection
tool, whatever. Now let's focus on this thumbnail first.
So let's just get this right real quick.
Again, not very ideal.
I don't want to... maybe I should make this smaller just because
I feel like it... I feel like maybe I'm making them a bit too
big sometimes. To the point where it feels
unnatural. Okay,
let
me try to make it bigger
now. No. Yeah,
I wish, I wish he just held his laptop a bit,
because I don't think we can cleanly cut it out in this case.
Just because, like, the shadows there are gonna be messed up and his hand
also. Uhm,
that, okay, I'm gonna let Gus know this,
that the guests should be taking their photos
better. You know,
I'm thinking it should be somewhere in the middle almost.
Like this big for the photo and then this big for the text.
I like this,
okay. So,
we'll just go ahead, do auto adjust,
then I'll duplicate this,
BG remover, and
yeah, this is unusable. Okay,
now, Now. Let's
grab this shading tool, although Pat mentions that
the shading sometimes makes the backgrounds look AI,
which makes sense. But I think
if we have it subtly, like that, then it actually helps.
Now, we'll just
brighten him up. Potentially,
a bit of,
ooh, yeah, this looks better. We don't wanna,
Do it too much. We don't wanna do
saturation too much either. Maybe vibranze,
not saturation.
Awesome. I love this.
What kind of, I do for,
I don't think we can remove the screen here.
I think this thumbnail is just gonna be super simple.
Um,
we're just gonna leave this one as is. I would love
to do an iteration where,
it's a, It's
no text, and we just have a graphic
on the screen, but here it's not gonna work just because he's holding his
laptop that low. So,
we'll experiment with this one though, and I'll start a new room for that.