Okay, here, we'll follow the same exact process.
So, usually,
yeah, honestly, the main thing is just,
like, the composition. When you get the composition right,
the thumbnail looks so much better. Here,
the same exact thing. I would love to have his thumb higher.
That's It's kind of like the problem with, With the thumbnails always,
just because when you're taking the photo in real life,
it feels super weird to lift your thumb higher.
But on the thumbnail, it actually looks better.
So, I have a few thoughts here. First of all,
I have a cool idea. Or
maybe this isn't a cool idea,
but at least it's an idea.
Because,
you know, see how he has text on his screen?
So, if it wasn't this text-heavy,
I would just kind of, like, do this,
and then I would say 34k per month if he didn't have that, or
17k per month,
whatever
he makes, if he didn't have,
That text on the,
on the screen, but with the text, it just looks a little bit too
busy. So what I'm thinking,
I know what we'll do, but we need Photoshop for this again.
We'll do this in Photoshop though, it's gonna be worth it.
I think this is gonna be gonna turn out really good.
Uhm,
yeah, honestly, getting the composition right is,
And I just can't find this thumbnail now.
Getting the composition right,
I don't even need this Anymore?
I don't think so. Let me save it just in case.
Uhm,
getting the composition right really is the biggest challenge.
But, once you do get it right,
the thumbnail just becomes so much better.
And Photoshop, truthfully, is a lot better for this.
Uh, and, uhm, and you'll see right now why.
So what I wanna do, is I wanna,
What's a nice scale, you think?
I think it's something like this.
Potentially even having it
like this. Yeah, yeah, yeah, this is gonna look really cool.
Okay, nice. And now we'll do a bunch of masking.
So, what we need to do first,
is we need to, Honestly,
remove the guy.
I probably should have done it from the very beginning,
but that's okay. We need to remove the guy,
and it's definitely not gonna be ideal.
Honestly, if I just, like, select subject.
Uh,
I'll deselect all this.
Perfect.
Uhm, can I,
see, I don't know how to use Photoshop.
I just wanna, like, exp-, maybe select and mask.
Yeah, now it's just not working. Nice.
Dude,
what the hell,
what the hell
happened?
I couldn't, I didn't have a chance to, like,
select anything. Okay. Yeah,
so I'll Shift-Edge. And this definitely
doesn't help that much. Okay,
whatever, I'll just, I'll just press Remove and hope for the best.
I don't know what, what it's going to come up with.
Hopefully something. Something half decent,
probably. Oh shit,
this is perfect. Wait,
this is literally all we need. Okay.
Oh, but now it's annoying because.
Ah, yeah, see this is what happens when you have no idea what you're
doing. Sorry about
this. Okay.
You know what? I'll just,
I'll just. Start from scratch.
I think this is going to be better. So.
So I'll open this.
Yeah, see, I don't even know,
like, how to start a new thing. Can
I f******. Did one sec.
Okay, never mind. This Photoshop AI is so good.
I don't even need to do any of that. It literally did this,
which is pretty cool. F****** crazy. All right,
so we have this, which is an awesome start.
Now, my plan is to move this.
Yeah, I need, I need to, I need to select the guy here on
this layer. Uhm,
I don't need to say it. Select the monitor.
My plan is to basically move the monitor down,
and like the background down, so that we have space
on top to put the 17k
per month and whatnot text.
Is
this good? I think so.
All right, so we don't need this. We need to move this
down. Like that.
How much down?
Probably like this.
Just so you can tell that it's a monitor.
But we have space to put 17k per month there on top.
Okay, uh,
now let me figure out how to, uhm,
think about I just,
I think I, hopefully I can just do this and do Generative Fill and
then just like generate
Yeah, this is kind of the thing about Photoshop versus Canva is Photoshop Generative
Fill is so much better and also Canva doesn't have masking.
At least I don't know about it. Alright,
this is good, and now the final touch of
all this is I want his thumb.
So I'll go ahead, I'll duplicate the,
I'll duplicate the initial layer,
I'll move it bit up, I'll just, select,
I can select his whole hand.
Perfect. Yeah,
see how much better it looks when he's,
like, I wish, I wish, I wish they would know that while taking
the thumbnail, but you, you just never know.
And it's, you know, it's understandable.
and On this thing,
I'll just remove it.
The only thing is, should have done it before
this. Let's
see what it comes up with. Maybe it's,
again, maybe I'm just underestimating how good it is.
Holy shit,
I, uhm, I didn't think that it would draw his exact,
like, edge of his body. Oh my god,
it's so good. It's insane.
It's insane. Alright,
now we're done. That's it.
I don't want to blur this, although,
maybe just like a tiny bit. Thank Let's see.
Yeah, nah, because it's on the same distance from the
camera as his face. So,
we don't want to blur it, we just want to export as
JPEG, quality high.
And, uhm, I'll save it as is.
Cool.
And now, yeah,
and by the way, just to show you the difference,
why we did all that is because we went from this to this.
And this is so much better composition-wise.
And, still, what's, by the way, what's so important,
okay, because Pat mentioned it, Pat mentioned this a bunch of times,
is, like, we don't want to make stuff look AI.
So, if you imagine, this is still,
this still looks very realistic. Like, you can take a photo like that,
it's just his camera wasn't positioned ideally,
which is a fair point. Like,
you, you never know while taking the photo.
So, you ideally want to fix that in post.
But it makes composition so much better.
Like, we, you know, here I
can't really do anything. If I want to follow my idea of,
okay, I want to put text here on the top,
I need to have the guy that low and then I can't see his
thumb. Which, I guess, honestly,
it's okay if I just remove his thumb.
His thumb from here.
This is actually not bad at all.
Maybe I should just remove his thumb because his thumb
is kind of annoying. Maybe I should move it lower.
Yeah, so that it's a bit less. Maybe I should make this a bit
lower as well. I'll move this a bit
lower. Uhm,
but again,
if you don't want to mess around with it that much,
then I guess you can just position it like this. Then the guy is
a bit lower than ideally I would want.
I don't want to have it personally, but at least you have space on
the top to put the text there.
And then you obviously just, like, remove his thumb and you can do this
in Canva. So, this would be super possible in Canva.
Canva would remove this thumb easily.
And then you would just generate the,
uhm,
like, the border.
But now, since we already went through all this,
let me just real quick generate this
and we'll finally finalize this,
uh, this in Canva. Finalizing in Canva is
much easier than in Photoshop. Uh,
this is kind of like my workflow in general,
is you wanna, if you wanna mess around with
composition, like this, then you do it in Photoshop.
And then, in terms of adding the text and stuff like that,
you just do it in Canva, because it's just, it's just easier and
faster. And honestly, the result,
maybe it's because I don't know how to use Photoshop again.
But, That's
the way I do it. So, I'll
import this. Perfect.
Uh, I'll do the color correction right away.
Let me just do, I
don't like it, because it washed it out,
so I'll, I'll separate it.
Although, maybe I'm just being lazy.
I just need to, just need to not let it wash it out.
Yeah,
it's gonna,
it's gonna
be better
now that I separate it.
Let
me copy the thing.
I don't wanna darken the monitor by too much.
Since it's kind of like,
you know, a part of the thumbnail.
What I'll do now is,
yeah, I'll just copy this text. I'll
put, per month, I think,
on top of the monitor, maybe like here.
Yep. And-
It says 17k, and again,
the font is just annoying.
going.
I'll make this as big as I can,
really. This is pretty good.
Hmm. Per month doesn't fit.
What I would do in these scenarios is I would usually just make it
MRR instead.
Like this.
Ooh, this is good. I love this.
Okay. So then the last thing,
I'm just gonna
make sure this is, Align
like this nicely. Essentially,
nah, it doesn't need to be bigger. I'm just gonna put it on top
of the monitor like that. And then,
yeah, MRR is gonna be here,
let's see. I think,
I want to have MRR there.
And because of that,
I'm gonna make this text a bit bigger.
And now I'm starting to think that the monitor should be shaded a bit
more. Or,
Maybe I should just wash it out more.
If I go to,
which one is it? This one. And I'll bring down the
white.
So that this text on the monitor doesn't,
you know. No. Interferes with this white text
enama. I'm also starting to think that,
it was better like this to create more separation kind of.
Cause you don't, you don't want this text that you've added and then text
from the monitor to clash. Yeah.
Cool. Now,
the shadow needs a bit of tweaking. Let's see what's happening.
Wait, which direction should it be?
Like this, right? Probably minus forty-five,
yeah. Alright. Cool.
And I would say this needs a bit less.
Although, nah, it was actually good.
Sweet. Uh, the,
the last thing. Is an arrow.
We can reuse this arrow. But what we want to do for this arrow
is, I would really make it,
umm,
I would grab this color. Nope,
it should be, the other way around.
And potentially make this,
this should be white. All right. Like that.
I like this more.
Yeah,
this is better. Uh, maybe honestly, instead of this purple, I should- . Nah,
purple, purple is cool. Uh,
awesome. Think that's it.
Just to quickly recap, Composition is the main thing.
And then really just wrapping it up,
making sure that, The subject and the text stand
out. Here, actually, I like,
I like more when it's shaded. You still
can't tell that this is a monitor. Maybe a bit less,
like that. But you still can't tell that this is a monitor,
which is the main thing. Mmm.
And yeah, that's it, we do.