Alright, so we're creating the third thumbnail over here and,
uhm, the title is How I Built It,
16k per month, MicroSaaS. Pick a specific niche,
not a generic market.
Okay, so it's basically just gonna be 16k per month,
uhm, app. And,
uhm, yeah, let's check out the photos.
Bye. I already have them downloaded over here.
Okay, so what I don't like about all
of, about these four is that you see
how far away he is from the camera.
Here, the same thing. Here,
he's much closer, which is a lot nicer.
And, uh, here,
yeah, I would say, I would say these four are not really usable just
for that reason that is too far.
In
terms of his face, I probably like this one the most.
This one can be good. We're gonna see how it is with,
We're
gonna see how it is with framing. Uh,
there is a thumbnail that is,
I think, gonna have a very similar vibe to this one.
Uhm, it's this. I think it's,
this one's gonna turn out pretty similar. So,
let's open up Canva. And,
uhm, yeah,
try it out, try out creating this thumbnail.
Okay,
so I'll import this photo first,
the one that I like the most. He
has his, I
would do an A-B test here.
I would have, Yeah,
because, like, his hand,
We might need to Photoshop it again.
I think that's gonna be the case.
Because without his hand,
it's just a little bit weird,
although we're gonna try it. But I think it's just gonna be better
if we Photoshop his hand and have him,
like, here. And then
have his hand over here.
I think it's gonna look natural and
not AI. Let's try
this photo. Yeah,
I'm not the biggest fan of this photo.
Although,
we can do this potentially, but I'm not sure if AI is gonna be
able to generate his hand nicely there.
Yeah. Okay. Uh,
so.
Should we, should we
pull up Photoshop then right away? Let's do it.
All right. So I just have this photo over here.
And, um, I'm going to do the same exact thing.
I'm just gonna do the
framing and the composition in Photoshop.
Yeah, I think this is definitely going to be the best,
the best one. And then we potentially,
yeah,
this is actually going to be a really good thumbnail,
I think. Uhm,
we just need to, just need to
take his hand, do
this, layer via copy.
Oh
yeah, this is better. I
think it's quite important here to really,
like, make sure the cutout looks great,
uh, just because again the
main idea is with the thumbnails is that we
don't want to make them look AI,
we just want to make it look as
if this guy has
taken the photo in a exactly
this way. Alright, I'll clean this up and then get
back to you.
Alright, I
think it looks pretty good now. I'll just put it,
I think it can be a
bit bigger.
And now, from this photo,
I'll, First of all,
I want to remove this AC that he has.
Just because it's annoying. Should
be very easy with AI.
Brilliant. And,
uh, oops. And then,
I'll just remove his hand as well.
That's
pretty ugly, but it works.
Okay, so,
yeah, we have his hand over here.
And, uh,
I want him to be positioned.
This way. Let me maybe, kind of,
like, do this. I think this
looks really good.
Uh,
what I'll do right now is,
Well, I'll just, I'll just do this,
and then I'll add this to
the selection, and I'll do Generative Fill.
And at this point, the photo is basically ready.
This is gonna be,
I would say, like, version 1.
Yeah, I like this one the best. Uh,
maybe it's a bit too much
space for text. Now that I think about
it, maybe, Maybe
not. Okay, I'll export this. This
is going to be our, let's say, V1.
Now, I just want to experiment a little
bit. I wanna, try
this, and then,
yeah, it's a bit annoying because the masking
isn't gonna be good again. So I would need to tweak it again.
Yeah,
maybe we just leave this.
Because I wanted to try moving him,
like, closer to the middle.
But then,
I don't
know how
to do this
in Photoshop.
I guess I can just do this, right? Does that look good?
I think so. Let me just clean up this
a tiny bit. Alright,
so this is gonna be our v2.
These aren't crazy different, so it's not like we're gonna be split testing
these. We're just gonna see which one turns
out better. And then for the split
test, what I wanna
try is, potentially, just like.
this, where it's not gonna have any text.
It's gonna be centered. Let's make
sure that it's centered. I think it is.
Uh, because, yeah,
it looks pretty good. We obviously need to remove this,
ugly. Ugly hands.
I would say,
I would say
I want to remove. Nice,
now we should be able to,
yeah, grab his hand like this.
Again,
it's a bit annoying that I'm, like,
literally all of this is because he has no has just taken the photo
in a bit of a suboptimal way.
But, I think it will make the thumbnail
And it shouldn't be,
Yeah, I guess, honestly, this might be un-Photoshopable.
Or at least, at least,
you know, I'm just not, not that good at Photoshop.
Yeah, I think it's gonna, it's, it looks ugly.
Okay. Then,
I guess, let's just roll with the
regular one. Uh,
what I'll do here in Photoshop, though,
is I'll just make sure that,
oh, I wish his hand was closer.
But I think this is a good A-B test.
If we just have it with no,
no text, no nothing. So let
me do this real quick and then I
would like to I'm
gonna leave this small bit but then I
want to remove this window.
And hopefully this is something.
Oops, I did it wrong.
Hopefully this is something AI
can do. Let's see.
This is pretty perfect.
Wait,
why did it?
Okay, because I didn't select it.
Let me. Make sure. Make sure that I don't select any of this.
And then I'll select this.
Should be pretty good now.
Alright, whatever. It generates this small bit,
but I don't think it matters that much. So,
uhm,
now this is going to be our V3. And basically,
yeah, we will do, we'll do two,
We'll do an A-B test of two thumbnails,
the version one,
the main version
is going to be this photo,
just because it looks better than this one.
Yeah, this one definitely looks better.
Maybe we can, now I'm starting to,
to think that it's too close, which it probably
is. Oh,
but I, I literally removed everything.
That's not ideal.
Wait,
let me try. I want to have
it a bit closer to the center.
So, potentially,
like this.
Okay,
yeah, I like this. Uh,
this is gonna be, I mean,
I'll name it, V4 But basically,
right now, finally, let's go to Canva and we're gonna have this
Let me just show you the difference. So,
this is the one that's, I think is the best Here it's his way
too far to the left and the hand doesn't look that good And
if we compare these two, we just moved him closer to
the left But honestly, what happens,
What might happen is we're just gonna find out right now that it's actually
better to have him closer on the left And then we'll use the
other one. But for now, let's try this one And
so what I'll do is I'll just copy the text And
the arrow, the everything Yeah,
I like this more, because then we can make the text bigger.
This is why it's nice to have,
you know, a few variations.
Sorry,
one sec. Okay,
uhm,
yeah, the text is a bit, I
don't know, it seems a bit rotated.
I guess, I guess it's okay. Yeah,
I was saying that, that's why it's nice to have,
you know, just a few options for you to play around with,
in terms of the composition, like, here you can tell that this composition is
a lot better, just because we can actually fit in this text on screen
properly. So, uh,
I'll just remove that one, uh,
for the, yeah, for the arrow,
I quite like making it,
or I guess we're, we're gonna color, uh,
correct the screenshot and then we'll make the arrow.
For now, we'll just put it here, and now let's,
let's color grade. So,
let's see what this does.
It's okay. Let's do the BG remover
thing, and now we'll definitely add the shadow here
and here we need to yeah,
we need to add contrast, but not so much.
I
think it's better in this case. Yeah,
it's just not moving. Let's
create it in Photoshop. Wait one sec. Okay.
Just because his lighting isn't ideal.
And what I don't like here is that it,
like, it makes his screen overexposed.
And so I think it makes it a tiny bit worse.
Wait,
what the hell happens? I just wanna see,
I just wanna see, like, a difference.
Maybe I'm overthinking it, I don't know, maybe this is as good as it
can get. Because yeah,
his lighting definitely isn't ideal.
Nah,
I think it's actually a lot better in Photoshop.
His, uh, his background here is too much.
But it's okay, just because we're gonna separate that anyway.
So it's not a big of a deal.
Let
me save this. V2.
Upgrade it.
Let me just try how it is.
Yeah, I'd say it's much better.
If
you compare these two,
maybe I added a bit too much,
like, effects in Photoshop in terms of the
haze or whatever. Whatever it's called, and, like,
texture, but that's okay, I think. Uhm,
now finally, let's just grab this color.
Maybe,
maybe the other
way around?
I'll make, I'll make it like this.
Okay,
where
is it? Is it here?
That's it. Let's do the same thing with,
I don't know how to use Photoshop. Okay, perfect. I can do this. Nice.
No, it's not this one.
I need this one for the AB
test. Yeah,
I think it's too much. I overdid
it a little bit on the previous one.
I'll keep it like this. And then I'll not, not add as much of
these effects. Yeah.
Okay,
that's pretty good. And now we should be able to just put this into
Canva. Yeah, this thumbnail
actually looks pretty
good. Here
in Canva, we just need to do BG remover.
And then I think we can copy style from here on to here.
And then we can paste. Paste this as well.
And maybe it needs more.
Yup. And it needs more shadows.
Think
this is pretty good. One last thing I want to try,
just because on this thumbnail per day I
actually ended up outperforming everything in the,
in the A-B test.
So let me see if we divide 16 by 2.
30, 53 bucks,
or 500,
whatever, 533.
Let
me make a duplicate text here.
Okay.
Can make this text a bit bigger.
All right, perfect. I think this is it.
I'm gonna test out all three.
And, uh, yeah,
that's it for this thumbnail.