Alright,
so we're in Photoshop now, uh,
let's see, let's see what we can cook
up here. So the vision for this is why we're using Photoshop is because
his photo is, again,
not ideal where ideally you would have the camera kind of like tilted
so that you can see more Okay. His laptop in,
in frame, uh, if we look at this thumbnail,
for example, you can see how much closer his laptop is to his face.
So that's what we're gonna try and fix in Photoshop
while still having it look natural just because that's really,
that's really the big thing. The biggest thing for these thumbnails.
Not to make them look AI. Okay,
you know what?
I can even,
I can even use just the rule of thirds that I have set. Saved.
Oh, yeah, it's perfectly on the rule of thirds.
Uhm,
this might be a bit too big.
Yeah, just because you kind of want to see his table,
if you like, a little bit. Like this.
Then you want to frame it nicely. And now,
it should be super easy to just take his laptop
like that. And I'll just cut
it out.
Let's, let's see. So it needs to be,
if we imagine how it would be actually
in real life, it would probably be,
Wait, do I have his whole laptop there?
No, he has, Wait,
Cool, cut. I cut out in a weird way. Or I cut it out
in a weird way. Should have the full thing.
Can I make it snap to the bottom?
I
don't know how much better it looks. Maybe I
should do this. Just like, cover his laptop
like this. I think that's way too big
though. I feel
like it
should
be this
big, roughly.
And,
I mean, let's just hope that if
I duplicate this, this layer, and I
try to content-aware
fill his laptop, it's gonna do a good job.
Uhm,
960, right? I don't know,
does
this look AI?
I mean, it definitely looks better,
but, I'm just not sure if it looks realistic.
And yeah, we definitely want to do a bit of a better job cutting
out this laptop.
Please help, let me, please help. Play around with
Where
Dude, what the hell? So
we don't need to cut out that much because on the bottom
it has this white outline. But you know,
since we don't need the bottom. Oh
yeah, this is so much better.
Damn. Oh damn,
this looks actually really good. Oh damn, look at this. We
want to have it perfectly centered,
just like that, and then potentially,
what about we add this Apple glowing
thing, uhm,
Apple logo, PNG.
This
might take a while, just because I'm a newbie in Photoshop,
but hopefully I'll figure it out.
So,
I have no way, why is it
that small?
Is it good quality? Yeah,
it is, okay. So,
first we wanna, Well,
yeah, I know in Photoshop you can,
You can just do solid color.
Then you can do this, and then you can do this.
And now what I'll do And then
know what? Uhm,
let me try to do it the proper way.
I know that somehow. You wanna have it
basically. But
then, I don't know what to do here.
Yeah, it just didn't do anything. One
sec, let me figure this out. Okay,
I just ended up manually doing it basically.
And of what I'll do.
Right now, I think it's pretty close.
I think if I just apply
some Gaussian blur.
Hell yeah.
That's clean. I love this.
How do I remove this
thing? Okay,
this looks really good. We basically went from
this to this,
which is so much better. And his hands don't
look any AI, which is the most important thing ever.
So I tried to, or I can try to color grade this in Photoshop.
Honestly, I wouldn't.
Let me just save this real quick,
just in case. Just
because, I don't know, maybe I should.
Let me,
yeah, maybe I should color grade this in
Premiere,
or, sorry, in Photoshop.
Let
me export this. Just
because, you know, in Canva, I feel like,
really, it looks, it ends up looking like
a little bit,
I don't know, not,
not cinematic, necessarily.
Potentially even a bit, a tiny bit AI.
So if I go to Camera Raw Filter,
and I just, Auto. And then, I add a tiny bit of Lens
Blur. Thank you
There
is some Lens Blur already,
but I think we need a tiny bit more.
worth to add. Hmm,
I can't see a vignette here. I think it's worth to add,
Now I'm starting to think that this laptop is too big.
Yeah, the color grading definitely makes a difference.
Yeah, I'm starting to think that this laptop is too big.
Let me just, make it a tiny
bit smaller.
I mean, this definitely looks
more realistic,
but I don't like that, with his hands.
Yeah,
wait, this actually, this actually looks better.
Where is the center again?
Yeah,
this is that center.
for his hands to,
to seem like he's actually working,
instead of kind of like resting there.
This
might be better, actually.
Let's
generate another one.
Oh, yeah, and this,
this, this laptop is definitely better.
Okay, awesome. Uh, I'll just export this,
and then we'll color grade it in Canva,
just honestly, because it's easier and faster.
Final two. Let's go to Canva.
Why isn't it in?
Dude,
what the hell is this? Can you not open Photoshop?
Sorry about this. I don't know what's happening.
It just, it just doesn't get imported.
Okay, so all that's done is really color grading.
Let me, BG remover,
this guy. Oh yeah,
this is good. Okay, and it actually looks very realistic.
I love this. Dude,
this Photoshop guy is just trying
Okay, this is perfect. Honestly,
I love this thumbnail. Hmm,
okay, let's see what we can do. So I would bump up the,
the vibrance again. I
like to add a tiny bit of sharpness,
just because it adds that, like,
pop and clarity.
Not too much,
but still, you know, still a little bit.
Yeah, you don't wanna, you don't wanna make him too ADHD,
but I'm almost thinking that it's cause,
it's not necessarily the vibrance,
it's cause he gets too yellow.
Alright,
well let's see, let's see the before and after.
Yeah, yeah, it definitely makes a huge difference.
What if I,
Also adjust this? Wait,
what? What's,
what's happening?
on? don't get this. What,
what layer does it change? Yeah,
it was changing the other thumbnail the whole time.
I don't get how, how this works.
Okay, nice, it actually makes it a lot nicer when we,
Bump up saturation and stuff.
I think we'll go for something like this. Is
this good? Let's see how it was beforehand.
And everything, just nothing
seems to work. Why does it, anyways,
whatever. Yeah, it, uh, it definitely got a lot nicer,
maybe too much saturation in the background.
Yeah, maybe something like this, but also,
you know, we shouldn't overthink it too much.
Okay, I think,
yeah, I think we did a really good job on this thumbnail.
You know, we went from this photo,
which was not good.
Not even on the screen.
Or the laptop at least, wasn't even on the screen.
And we made it look really nice, but it still,
it still looks realistic. So, super happy about this.
And yeah, that's it.