Okay, I just realized, what we can't do for this thumbnail is,
to be fair, I think it's a bit too much text since we have
text on screen and then we have all this text here,
uhm,
I'm trying to find, like,
the biggest number that he says in the video,
it doesn't look like he says anything besides 17k per month,
which honestly sucks. Uh,
let's see what happens if you you multiply 17
times 12, 200k.
That's pretty good.
Ideally, we would use this, and maybe
grab this pink. Let's try.
Oh, hell yeah. This looks really good.
Uh, this just needs to be behind the guy.
And it potentially needs to be bigger.
Design-wise, I like this better,
but, uh, if he doesn't say 200k anywhere in the video,
then we obviously can't really use this.
And then, this is still solid. I would just,
I would just use the purple. Uhm,
and this one, perfect.